A Guide to the Central Richmond Association Archives, n.d.
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
Central Richmond Association Archives, n.d.
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
M 195
23.2 linear feet
Central Richmond Association
Administrative Information
Access
Any financial or personnel materials still in the collection are not available for research.
Acquisition Information
The materials were donated to the Department by the Henry Gonner, Executive Director of CRA, in August 1984. Additional materials were donated by Fran Johns in October of 1996.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Central Richmond Association is dedicated to enhancing the economic, civic and human vitality of the center of metropolitan richmond. Through leadership, advocacy and action, the Association and its members support and promote a sound and expanding business environment in Richmond's downtown.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of newspaper clippings, photographs, and event information.
Arrangement
Materials arranged in chronological order.
Contents List
- Clippings (Box 1)
- Clippings (Box 2)
- Clippings (Box 3)
- Clippings (Box 4)
- Photographs (Box 5)
- Photographs (Box 6)
- Blue Cross/Blue Shield-new building and membership (Box 7)
- Broad St. Methodist Church n.d. 11/64 (Box 7)
- Christian Fund New Building n.d. (Box 7)
  7/64-10/64, 8/65-9/65
- Old City Hall/New City Hall (Box 7)
- Civic Center Committee n.d. (Box 7)
  9/59, 5/62, 3/63, 10/64-1966, 1/68-2/68
- Coliseum (Box 7)
- Convention Center (Richmond Centre) n.d. 3/76-9/76 (Box 7)
- DMV Building (Box 7)
- Downtown Motor Inn n.d. (Box 7)
  3/62, 10/62-11/62, 8/63, 10/63, 1/64-6/64, 4/83
- F and M Building (Box 7)
- Groundbreaking Farm Bureau 200 W. Grace St. n.d. 1963, 1965 (Box 7)
- Federal Building dedication, groundbreaking 1959, 1962 (Box 7)
- Federal Reserve Bank (Box 7)
- Fidelity Reserve Bank (Box 7)
- Fidelity Bankers Life Building 9th and Main (Box 7)
- Franklin Towers n.d. 1965 (Box 7)
- Grace-Belvidere Apartments n.d. (Box 7)
  4/63, 7/63, 5/64, 2/65-3/65
- Hilton Hotel n.d. 1981-1983 (Box 7)
- Holiday Inn n.d. (Box 7)
  8/60, 12/60, 4/63, 4/64-10/64
- J. Seargant Reynolds Community College (Box 7)
- Jefferson Hotel, n.d. 1975-1983 (Box 7)
- Lexington Tower (Box 7)
- Marriott Groundbreaking n.d. (Box 8)
  2/82, 5/82, 10/82-1/83
- Metropolitan Hospital (Box 8)
- James Monroe Building (Box 8)
- Post Office, Brook Road (Box 8)
- Project One, n.d. 3/80-4/82 (Box 8)
- Richmond Renaissance, n.d. (Box 8)
  11/82, 3/83, 5/83
- Richmond Technical Center, n.d. 10/66 (Box 8)
- Salvation Army (Box 8)
- Science Museum of Virginia (Box 8)
- Sixth Street Mall, n.d. (Box 8)
  5/70-7/70,4/83-8/83
- Southern Band and Trust Co. (Box 8)
  7/68,4/70-6/70
- State Finance Building (Box 8)
- Old State Planters National Bank 11/81-6/83 (Box 8)
- UVB (United Virginia Bank) n.d. 9/69 (Box 8)
- Va Hospital (Veterans Administration) (Box 8)
- Valentine Museum n.d. 8/66-9/66 (Box 8)
- Site for the VEC (UCC) Building (Box 8)
  2/60,5/60-6/60
- VEC Groundbreaking and Open House; Local Office 6/61, 11/62 (Box 8)
- Virginia Power Building (Box 8)
- Downtown Marketing Committee, n.d. 9/81-11/81 (Box 9)
- Miscellaneous (Box 9)
- News Releases (Box 9)
- CRA Membership Publication Straight from the Heart 5/58-12/65 (Box 9)
- Straight from the Heart 3/66, 1983 (Box 9)
- CRA Business No. 10 (Box 9)
- CRA Meetings and Minutes (Box 9)
- Miscellaneous to be filed (Box 9)
- News Releases (Box 9)
- To be filed (Box 9)
- To be filed (Box 9)
- Western Electric Plant (Box 9)
- Western Electric Plant (Box 9)
- CRA Marketing Survey (Box 9)
- Feasibility Report for Flood Control (Box 9)
- Parking Board (Box 9)
- Main-to-the-James Market Plan (Box 9)
- Van pool-Commuter Groups Transportation (Box 10)
- Strotmeyer and Epps (Box 10)
- Virginia Mutual S and L-opening celebration 11/77 (Box 10)
- Junior League HQ-205 W. Franklin (Box 10)
- Cable TV (Box 10)
- Golden Wings over Richmond Air Show (Box 10)
- I-295 (interstate) (Box 10)
- Transit Co. Tour (Box 10)
- 9th Street Bridge (Box 10)
- Touchdown Club (Box 10)
- Fight Litter Campaign; Operation Clean Sweep 4/70, 1/71 (Box 10)
- Smithdeal-Massey Re-Opening 6/75 (Box 10)
- CNB Commercial Road 6/71-7/71 (Box 10)
- June Jubilee (Box 10)
- Downtown Improvement Measeures (Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority) n.d. 72-73 (Box 10)
- Econologue Panel Discussion 9/73 (Box 10)
- CRA Membership List 1972 (Box 10)
- Virginia Building Mgrs. Assn. n.d. 5/76 (Box 10)
- Petersburg Revitalization, n.d. 12/73-3/74 (Box 10)
- Sears Talk, n.d. 3/74-4/74 (Box 10)
- Sears new auto service garage; closes, n.d. (Box 10)
  2/74-4/74,4/73,3/81-10/81
- Economic Progress, Building Projects, n.d. 3/82-5/83 (Box 10)
- Navy-CRA Day, n.d. 10/64 (Box 10)
- All American City 1967 (Box 10)
- Capitol Street Mall 3/82 (Box 10)
- Heart of the Core-Ad Hoc Development Group 1975 (Box 10)
- Shopper Survey of Downtown Workers 1976 (Box 10)
- Early CRA (Boushall's File) (Box 10)
- Riverfront Development, n.d. (Box 10)
  5/78,7/81,12/81-2/82
- LEe Bridge, n.d. (Box 10)
  10/74,1/78,6/78,11/79,6/81-5/83
- New Executive Welcome, n.d. 9/78-10/78 (Box 10)
- Tower Construction Co. Membership, n.d. 8/78-10/78 (Box 10)
- Shockoe Slip Great Pumpkin Party 10/78 (Box 10)
- Arts District Foundation, n.d. 3/83, 5/83 (Box 10)
- Developers guest at CRA meetings, n.d. (Box 10)
  1/79,9/79-6/80,1/82-2/82,8/83
- State Association, n.d. 2/83-6/83 (Box 10)
- U of R purchase Baptist Church 6/68 (Box 10)
- U of R purchase Baptist Church 6/68 (Box 10)
- Vepco buys nearby properties 3/66 (Box 10)
- Flower Carts, n.d. 4/65-4-66 (Box 10)
- Board of Directors, n.d. (Box 10)
  11/68,7/70-2/71
- Gracefest, n.d. 10/79 (Box 10)
- Flags, n.d. (Box 10)
  9/63-1/64,12/68-5/69
- James and Kanawha Canal (Box 10)
- Uniform Building Maintenance Code Committee 4/83-6/83 (Box 10)
- Salvation Army Study Committee, n.d. 5/78-10/78 (Box 10)
- Stadium (clippings) 1/80, 1983 (Box 10)
- Directors getting membership, n.d. (Box 10)
  3/72,7/76,10/78-7/79
- Metropolitan Richmond Chamber of Commerce 9/78 (Box 10)
- Second Quarterly Board of Meeting, n.d. 1/78-9/78 (Box 10)
- New Executive Welcome, n.d. 8/81, 1983 (Box 10)
- The New Mall (1620 W Main) 5/83 (Box 10)
- Revitalization News-Urban Renewal Publications, n.d. 3/83, 6/83 (Box 10)
- Executive Committee, n.d. 5/83 (Box 10)
- Sam Miller's Opening and Closing, n.d. 4/83 (Box 10)
- Universal Motor, n.d. 5/64 (Box 10)
- Universal Leaf Tobacco Co. 3/64 (Box 10)
- Union Building 6th and Franklin 1963-1965 (Box 10)
- GRTC's Central Business District List of Occupants 1977-1978 (Box 10)
- National Insurance Assn. 50th Anniversary 6/70 (Box 10)
- Lane Bryant Store (Box 10)
- Jackson Ward (Box 10)
- Blues Armory, n.d. 2/65, 9/65 (Box 10)
- Who's Who in Metropolitan Richmond 1/60, 4/70 (Box 10)
- Streetscape (Box 10)
- Questionaire on Downtown Store Hours (Box 10)
- Sprucing up 2nd to 3rd Street; Revitalization of Downtown (Box 10)
- Finance Budget CRA 1970-71, 1967 (Box 10)
- Wings over Richmond-Byrd Airport 10/77 (Box 10)
- CRA Goals, Budgets, Resolutions, Finance (Box 10)
- Taxes (Box 10)
- Shelters for Homeless (Box 10)
- 17th Anniversary (Box 10)
- Times-Dispatch series; Old City Buildings Going12/70 (Box 10)
- Econologue (Box 10)
- New CBD (Central Business District) Publications (Box 10)
- Fashion in Progress (Box 10)
- Milestones of Progress 1961 (Box 10)
- Facts on Downtown Richmond Assets 8/76 (Box 10)
- Downtown Commission Economic Study (Box 10)
- Fred Fay-Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority, n.d. (Box 10)
  9/70,7/71,10/71
- Lewis Powell, n.d. 10/71-1/72 (Box 10)
- Rail Pax-Richmond Link 12/70, 2/71 (Box 10)
- 3rd Quarter New Executive Welcome, n.d. 5/81-9/81 (Box 10)
- Board of Directors Meeting-2nd Quarter, n.d. (Box 10)
  7/78,6/81-7/81
- Annual Downtown Data Systems Committee (ADDS), n.d. (Box 10)
  7/80,9/80-12/80,3/81-7/81,10/81
- 3rd Quarter Board Meeting (Box 10)
  10/80,4/81,9/81-10/81
- City Council Parking Hotel Coliseum, n.d. 12/70 (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous-to be filed (Box 11)
- Virginia Downtown Development Assn. (Box 11)
- Commonwealth Park Hotel (Box 11)
- U of R Sesquicentennial (Box 11)
- Virginia Mutual Insurance Co. (Box 11)
- Downtown Marketing Survey 1976-1977 (Box 11)
- Richmond Braves (Box 11)
- Richmond Arts District (Empire Theater and Environs) (Box 11)
- Leadership Metro Richmond (Box 11)
- Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike (Box 11)
- Old Mansion Coffee Building 9/82 (Box 11)
- West Sand and Gravel Grand Opening (Box 11)
- Norfolk Officials visit Richmond (Box 11)
- John Marshall Convention Center (Box 11)
- Bank of Virginia New HQ Grand Opening (Box 11)
- Lighting Downtown (Box 11)
- Richmond Vees (Virginians)-Braves Baseball Team (Box 11)
- CSX Corp. (Box 11)
- Gracefest/Streetscape (Box 11)
- Free Parking Downtown (Box 11)
- Figgie International (nee A-T-O) (Box 11)
- Stadium location Committee (Box 11)
- Inner City Stadium Committee (Box 11)
- Galeski Photo Center (Box 11)
- Metropolitan Hospital Area Progress Committee (Box 11)
- Cable TV (Box 11)
- Red Cross/United Way (Box 11)
- Lee Bridge (Box 11)
- Leigh Street Extension (Box 11)
- Annual Downtown Data Systems Committee 1980, 1981 (Box 11)
- Floodwall (Box 11)
- Flood Meeting (Box 11)
- Flood Prevention (Box 11)
- Newman's Store Racial Issue-NAACP demands (Box 11)
- Senior Citizen's Day 5/75 (Box 11)
- Summer Jobs Program (Box 11)
- Arts and Crafts show (Box 11)
- Tobacco Festival (Box 11)
- Fall Frolics, Country Comes to Town, Shockoe Art Show events (Box 11)
- IDEA International Downtown Executive Area Assn. (Box 11)
- CRA 25th Anniversary (Box 11)
- Stuart Circle Hospital-groundbreaking 10/77 (Box 11)
- Waterfront Restaurant on the James (Box 11)
- Freight Station Shopping Mall (Box 11)
- VCU Expansion (Box 11)
- James Center (Box 11)
- Metropolitan Economic Development Council (Box 11)
- RMA-Downtown Expressway #2 (Box 11)
- RPI-VCU Residence Center (Box 11)
- CRA Staff-Job Descriptions, Salaries, etc. (Box 11)
- Heart of the Core Development Group (Box 11)
- Edgar Allen Poe Museum (Box 11)
- Plant Trees on Main Street (Box 11)
- Heliport Committee, n.d. (Box 12)
  2/65-9/65,3/66-7/66,11/66,6/67-8/67,11/67,3/68
- Downtown Development Commission, n.d. (Box 12)
  9/74,11/74-4/75,8/75
- Transportation 10/65, 2/70, 1981 (Box 12)
- CRA Parking, Traffic and Transportation Committee, n.d. (Box 12)
  1/66,9/66-11/66,9/67,2/68,7/68,1/69-7/70
- Transportation Center, n.d. 1980-1981 (Box 12)
- Helicopter Tour-Transportation 2/70 (Box 12)
- Coliseum Parking (Box 12)
- Transportation and Parking (Box 12)
- VIP (Visual Improvement Project) and Downtown Improvement 3/75-4/75 (Box 12)
- Richmond Resources Committee, n.d. 11/76-4/77 (Box 12)
- Albemarle Paper Meeting (Addition/Remodeling) 1964-1965 (Box 12)
- Dietz Press, Inc., n.d. 5/64 (Box 12)
- Major Medical Insurance Plans for CRA Employees, n.d. 1972-1973 (Box 12)
- Southside Plaza Carwash, n.d. 1971 (Box 12)
- Coliseum/North Core Development Plans, n.d. 1969, 11/70 (Box 12)
- Rail Pax-Passenger Travel by Train, n.d. 12/70-1/71 (Box 12)
- Retraining Liggett and Meyers Unemployed 10/70-2/71 (Box 12)
- Topple the Tipple and RF and P's new rail yard, n.d. 6/58, 6/6112/62 (Box 12)
- Richmond Public Library (expansion and dedication), n.d. (Box 12)
  2/70,5/70,3/72,8/72-9/72
- Smithdeal Massey College New Expansion, n.d. (Box 12)
- Summaries of Major Building Projects, n.d. (Box 12)
- Engineer's Club 7/62 (Box 12)
- New State Planters Auto Bank, n.d. (Box 12)
  1/64,9/64,9/66,11/66
- Hermitage Road Improvements (Box 12)
  12/67,6/68,7/68,12/69
- Richmond's Building Boom, general, n.d. 7/61-2/68 (Box 12)
- New Dues Schedule, CRA Membership, n.d. 6/57-9/57 (Box 12)
- Legislative Round Table, n.d. (Box 12)
  4/74,1/78,1/79,1/80-2/80,1/81-2/81,1/82-3/82,1/83-2/83
- Metro Richmond University Site Evaluation 11/66 (Box 12)
- Urban landscapping-M. Paul Friedberg appearance 12/70 (Box 12)
- Merchandizing Meeting at Miller and Rhoads-Frederick Atkins, Inc. 10/70 (Box 12)
- Sixth St. Self-Park Garage, n.d. 9/70 (Box 12)
- I Love America Day- Richmond Honor America Day-Wash. D.C. 4th of July celebrations 6/70-8/70 (Box 12)
- Richmond Beautification (Box 12)
  5/56,5/57,5/60,9/60-1/61,7/62-1/63,9/63-11/63,5/64-6/65,9/65,8/66,1/67
- Richmond Convention and Visitors Bureau 1981 (Box 12)
- Shockoe Bottom Progress Committee, n.d. 1981 (Box 12)
- Project One Parking-on site of Marriott 5/81-6/81 (Box 12)
- Ross Building (Box 12)
- Sears, n.d. 6/66, 10/67 (Box 12)
- Everett Waddey grand opening and CRA meeting 6/60, 9/60 (Box 12)
- Public Safety and Security, n.d. (Box 12)
  11/72,11/73,11/74-3/75
- Dr. Jerry Cable-Tobacco Company, n.d. 6/76, 8/76 (Box 12)
- ABC New Building opening 6/76 (Box 12)
- Immigration and Naturalization Service (I.N.S), n.d. (Box 12)
  7-8/62,4/64,6/68-7/68,9/75-12/75,1/76,3/76
- Street Light Improvements Downtown 11/75 (Box 12)
- 1st and Cary office building, n.d. 1/67 (Box 12)
- Richmond Sports Boosters, n.d. 3/67, 11/67, 4/68 (Box 12)
- Downtown Parking Signs, n.d. 3/67-7/67 (Box 12)
- Tourist Center Info., n.d. 9/66, 11/66, 7/67 (Box 12)
- Self Park-7th and Marshall streets, n.d. 11/65, 4/66-7/66 (Box 12)
- Report on Central Business Districts from Intl Downtown Exec Assn material 9/73 (Box 12)
- Braves, n.d. (Box 12)
  4/61,6/62,9/62,4/63,4/64,5/65,4/67,1/70,3/81,11/81
- McKenzie Street Extension, n.d. 1960-1967 (Box 12)
- Immigration and Naturalization Service, n.d. (Box 12)
  1/64,9/74,2/75-1/76
- A Night in Richmond-Va. General Assembly Hospitality, n.d. (Box 12)
  10/66,11/67,1/68,1/69-4/70
- Opening McKenzie street 6/62-8/62 (Box 12)
- CRA visits Norfolk to see its urban renewal, n.d. (Box 12)
  6/60,7/62-9/62,4/63-5/63
- DMC (Downtown Marketing Committee) Efforts for Downtown Clean Sidewalks, n.d. 1/75, 3/75, 5/75 (Box 12)
- Second Street Parking Company 2/73 (Box 12)
- Fashion in Progress, n.d. 2/69-4/69 (Box 12)
- General Tire Opening, n.d. 7/65, 7/66 (Box 12)
- DRA Beautification, n.d. 3/63 (Box 12)
- East Central Richmond Progress Committee, n.d. (Box 12)
  4/62,7/62-9/62,2/63-3/63,7/63-9/63,5/64,7/64
- Interclub Council-Richmond Area 12/71, 11/75-12/75 (Box 12)
- Farmer's Market, n.d. 3/75 (Box 12)
- Factory Outlet Opening (formerly Raylass) 10/82 (Box 12)
- 8th and Main Building-Wheat First Securities 6/73, 8/73 (Box 12)
- Siegel's Supermarket Opening 11/67 (Box 12)
- River Towers Apt. Building 8/65 (Box 12)
- Va. Farm Bureau Federation, n.d. 2/62-11/65 (Box 12)
- Candlelighting Program (Box 12)
  6/59, 11/59, 11/60, 9/61
- Christmas Parade 1972 (Box 12)
- Model Neighborhood Program-Church Hill 6/73 (Box 12)
- Manchester Bridge-9th street 8/73 (Box 12)
- Metropolitan National Bank 7/65 (Box 12)
- 7th and Franklin Building 12/67-1/68 (Box 12)
- Kanawha Square 7/70 (Box 12)
- Central Location Committee-finding downtown office space, n.d. 4/68, 7/68 (Box 12)
- CRA Retail Sales Promotion Executive staff position 11/82 (Box 12)
- How to Develop a Downtown Shopping Center 11/74 (Box 13)
- Downtown Problems Study 10/74 (Box 13)
- Banquet (1st Annual) 11/59 (Box 13)
- Annual Downtown Data Systems Comm. 3-4/82 (Box 13)
- Shockoe Valley Progress 11/79, 11/80, 10/82 (Box 13)
- Shockoe Slip, n.d. (Box 13)
- Shockoe Slip Neighborhood Assn. 12/77 (Box 13)
- Free B, n.d. 11/73, 12/73 (Box 13)
- Retail Physical Appearance, n.d. (Box 13)
  10/57,4/60,8/60,10/60,11/60,5/62,1963
- Executive Committeed 1/82, 8/82 (Box 13)
- Teacher Convention-DRA Apple for the Teacher, n.d. 10-11/65 (Box 13)
- CRA History-Bylaws (Box 13)
  1950-68,1951,6/57,12/71
- Dr. Moeszer-Commonwealth Economics, n.d. 9/79, 8/80 (Box 13)
- Richmond-on-the-James 9/80 (Box 13)
- New Exec Welcome 11/78, 11/79, 3/79 (Box 13)
- Conventions in Richmond, n.d. (Box 13)
- Nominating Committee Membership, n.d. (Box 13)
  12/69,1/70,10/79,4/80,11/80,2/82
- Nominations, n.d. (Box 13)
  1/62,9/67-10/67,10/69,10/70-11/70,1/71,10/71-12/71,11/72-12/72,1/74,11/74-12/74,10/75-11/75,8/76,10/76-11/76,10/77-1/78
- Retail Merchants Assn., n.d. 11/80 (Box 13)
- Santa and Governor Dalton (Box 13)
  11/78,11/80,12/80,12/81
- Third Semi-Annual Seminar-Economic Impact, n.d. 9/79, 7-9/81 (Box 13)
- Formation Resolution of DRA (Downtown Retail Associates) (Retail Committee of CRA), n.d. (Box 13)
  6/57,7/58-12/58,2/59,6/59,8/59-9/59,1/60,4/60,9/60
- DRA History (Box 13)
  8/59,8/61,11/62,1963,12/63,1/64,2/71
- CRA-DRA Retail, n.d. (Box 13)
  7/58,1961,10/64,5/65,1/67,12/67,2/70,1/71-2/71,6/79
- CRA-DRA Pamphlets and Publications (Box 13)
- Belle of Richmond, n.d. (Box 13)
  5/81,3/82,6/82,12/82
- Rubber Tire Street Car (Trackless Trolley), n.d. (Box 13)
  3/82,5/82,6/82,7/82
- Free Buses 2/74 (Box 13)
- Easter 4/71 (Box 13)
- Main-to-the James, n.d. (Box 13)
  10/67,12/70,10/71,11/71,7/73,11/74,2/76,2/81,9/81,11/81,2/82,3/82
- Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike, n.d. 6/58, 7/59 (Box 13)
- RMA, n.d. (Box 13)
  6/65,2/66,8/66,4/73,2/74-5/74
- Opening of interstates 95 and 64 (connection of), n.d. 6/68 (Box 13)
- International Tobacco Conference 6/83 (Box 13)
- Kickoff for new Dash- GRTC bus route, n.d. 6/83 (Box 13)
- A.R.E.A. Construction Mgt. Corp. 10/82 (Box 13)
- Groundbreaking of MCV Hospital 6/77, 7/82 (Box 13)
- Downtown Marketing Committee 4/81, 6/82, 7/82 (Box 13)
- Beginning demolition of 2nd and Grace Street Parking Lot 4-8/63 (Box 13)
- Interstate Openings, Development, n.d. (Box 13)
  6/68,7/68,7/70,8/70,9/70,7/75
- Gateway Opening-I64 Entrance to Downtown, n.d. 5/68, 6/68 (Box 13)
- Expressway Syestem-RMA, Powhite Parkway, etc., n.d. (Box 13)
  10/66,2/67,4/68,5/72,12/73,7/75,4/78
- Richmond Urban Institute 3/79 (Box 13)
- The Richmond Plaza Building (formerly L and M) purchased by Delaware Co., n.d. 7/76 (Box 13)
- Housing in downtown Richmon (Box 13)
  1/81,5-7/81,11/81,2/82
- CRA Annual Meetings, n.d. 1/59, 1/60 (Box 13)
- CRA's 20th Anniversary at new city hall, n.d. 12/70, 4/71, 5/71 (Box 13)
- CRA's 23rd Annual Meeting 4/73 (Box 13)
- CRA's 30th Birthday, n.d. 8/79, 4/80, 5/80 (Box 13)
- The Berkshire 300 W. Franklin Street 4/60 (Box 13)
- New York Times Richmond Building Boom article 2/67, 3/67, 4/67 (Box 13)
- Main-to-the-James (con't), n.d. (Box 13)
  3/69,4/69,10/69,11/69,12/69,1-6/70,8/70,11/70,1-8/71
- Main-to-the-James Land Use Committee, n.d. 2/68, 12/70, 2/70 (Box 13)
- Main-to-the James Concept Plan Report 1972 (Box 13)
- Main-to-the-James, n.d. 2/70, 3/70, 10/73 (Box 13)
- Main-to-the-James (cont), n.d. (Box 13)
  6/70,4/75,5/75,3/82,5/82
- Downtown Showcase, n.d. 3/75, 4/75, 5/75 (Box 13)
- Main-to-the-James Citizen Advisory Committee 10/71 (Box 13)
- CRA Business, n.d. (Box 14)
  1960,1/60,6/60,8/61,5/62,6/62,8/62,10/62,10/63,12/63,5/64,1965,10/64,1966,4/66,1967,1968,4/68,5/68,6/68,8/68,10/68,1969,2/69,1970,2/69,10/69,4/70,7/70,8/70,9/70,1971,4/71,5/71,1972,1/73,9/73,11/73,1976,9/77,197 8,1/78,4/79,3/80,4/80,1981,1/81,10/81,12/82,10/82
- CRA Business #2 (Box 14)
  6/61,1/65,6/65,2/66,4/66,9/66,2/69,1970,3/70,7/70,8/71,1/73,1974,1/74,5/74,6/74,11/74,1975,1/75,9/75,10/75,12/75,1976,5/76,1977,1/77,3/77,4/77- 9/77,11/77,1/78,2/78,1/79,6/79,7/81,8/81,11/81,7/82,10/82,11/82,1983,5/83,9/91
- CRA Business #3, n.d. (Box 14)
  6/59,4/60,1960,6/61,8/61,1/62,8/62,10/62,2/63,6/63,8/64,3/65,1/66,4/66,3/67,10/67,11/67,1/68,1969,2/71,4/71,6/71,7/71,9/71,10/71,1/72,3/72,11/72,4/73,5/73,8/73,11/73,12/73,4/74,1/75,2/75,6/75,10/75,11/76,1/77,2 /77,3/79,1980,3/80,6/80
- CRA Business #4 (Box 14)
  1/60,8/60,1/64,8/64,1964,1/65,2/65,3/65,8/65,1/66,6/66,1968,5/69,10/69,11/69,12/69,12/71,6/72,7/72,1/73,2/73,4/73,5/73,9/73,11/73,1/74,3/74,4/74,9/78
- CRA Business #5, n.d. (Box 14)
  1961,7/63,8/63,8/64,11/65,1/66,9/66,2/67,10/67,5/67,1/68,1968,5/68,4/70,7/70,9/70,12/70,4/72,6/72,1973,6/73,1975,5/75,9/75,10/75,11/75,1976,1/76,2/76,3/76,5/76,6/76,10/76,11/76,12/76,1977,1/77,3/77,4/77,7/77,19 78,1/78,12/78,1/79,1980,3/80,4/80,6/80,10/80,1/81,3/81-7/81,10/81,12/81,3/82-5/82,7/82,9/82-11/82,5/83
- CRA Business #6 (Box 14)
  7/59,4/60,10/60,11/60,8/62,2/64,2/65,7/65,10/65,12/65,1966,12/66,1967,11/67,12/67,1/68,5/68,9/68,1968,1/69,2/69,4/69,6/69,10/69,12/69,1969,1/70,3/70,7/70,8/70,10/70,1970,1/71,5/71,11/72,2/73,3/73,1/74,4/74,5/74 ,6/74,11/74,1975,3/75,5/75,7/75,10/75-12/75,1976,1/76,2/76,3/78,11/79,12/79,3/80,1982,10/82,11/82
- CRA Membership Drive Materials, n.d. (Box 14)
  7/54,4/56,8/57,2/58-9/58,5/59,1/60,2/60,7/60,11/60,1/61,2/61,
- News Release, n.d. (Box 14)
  6/58,1-5/60,8/60,8/61,7/62,11/62,1-2/63,4/63,10/63,4/64,7/64,12/64,3-4/65,8/65,4/66,10/66,1/67,4/67,8/67,12/67,8/68,2/69,12/69,12/70,1-2/70,1-4/71,7/71,9/71,12/71,2/72,4/72,7/72,11-12/72,1/73,3- 7/73,10/73,12/73,6/74,10/74,12/74,1/75,4-6/75,8/75,1-2/76,4-6/76,11/76,4-7/77,8/77,10-12/77,12/77,1/78,11-12/78,1/79,1-2/80,4/80,8/80,12/80,1/81,7/81,12/81,10/82
- CRA Data Book 1987 (Box 15)
- Letters 1985-1987 (Box 15)
- Photos (to be filed later) (Box 15)
- Style Weekly Vol. 8 no. 5 (Box 15)
- Seal (Box 15)
- Trolley Tokens (Box 15)
- General Facts About Downtown (Box 15)
- Archival material from CRA's exhibit celebrating its 40th anniversary (Box 16)
- Archival material from CRA's exhibit celebrating its 40th anniversary, oversize (Box 16)